Guide to the Nassau County Cooperative Extension records, 1914-1962
Nassau County Cooperative Extension records, 1914-1962
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Nassau County Cooperative Extension records, 1914-1962.
3927
Cooperative Extension Association of Nassau County.
1 cubic ft.
Field reports, annual reports, audits.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes weekly field reports of county agents, annual reports, and Farm Department audits.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes weekly field reports of county agents, annual reports, and Farm Department audits.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cooperative Extension Association of Nassau County.
Subjects:
Agricultural extension work.
Places:
Nassau County (N.Y.)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Weekly Field Reports of County Agent (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Weekly Field Reports of County Agent, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Weekly Field Reports of County Agent, Jan. 1915-June 1915 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Weekly Field Reports of County Agent, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Weekly Field Reports of County Agent, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Agricultural Program, 1918 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Annual Report of County Agent, Jan. 1, 1918-Dec. 1, 1918 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Annual Report of County Agent and Farm Bureau, Dec. 1, 1918-Nov. 30, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Annual Report of Agricultural Activities, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Annual Report of Farm Bureau, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Annual Report of Farm Bureau, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Projects, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Annual Report of County Agent, Dec. 1, 1921-Oct. 1, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Annual Report of County Agent, Oct. 1, 1922-Nov. 20, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Annual Reports of Farm Bureau and Extension Workers, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Annual Reports of Extension Workers, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Annual Report of Farm Bureau and County Agent, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Annual Report of Farm Bureau and County Agent, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Annual Report Agricultural Activities, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Annual Report Agricultural Activities, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Annual Report Farm Bureau and County Agents, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Annual Report of County Extension Workers, Dec. 1, 1926-Nov. 30, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Annual Report of Farm Bureau and County Agent, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Annual Report of Farm Bureau and County Agent, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Annual Report of Farm Bureau and County Agent, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Annual Report of Farm Bureau and County Agent, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Report of Farm Bureau and Agents, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Examination and Audit of Farm Department, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Examination and Audit of Farm Department, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Examination and Audit of Farm Department, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Examination and Audit of Farm Department, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Examination and Audit of Farm Department, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Report on Audit of Farm Department, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Report on Audit of Farm Department, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Report on Audit of Farm Department, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Report on Audit of Farm Department, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Report on Audit of Farm Department, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Report on Audit of Farm Department, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Report on Audit of Farm Department, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Report on Audit of Farm Department, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Report on Audit of Farm Department, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Report on Audit of Farm Department, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Report on Audit of Farm Department, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Report on Audit of Farm Department, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Report on Audit of Farm Department, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Examination of Accounts, Dec. 1, 1955-Nov. 30, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Report on Audit of Agriculture Depertment, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Examination of Accounts, Dec. 1, 1956-Nov. 30, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Report on Audit of Agriculture Department, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Examination of Accounts, Aug. 1, 1958-Nov. 30, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Report on Audit, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Report on Audit, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Examination of Accounts of Agriculture Department, Dec. 1, 1959-Sept. 30, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Report on Audit, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Report on Audit, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Report on Audit, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Miscellaneous and undated (Box 1, Folder 58)